jibm.org 2018-03-17

# Privacy Policy | Journal of Islamic Business<br> and Management (JIBM)

Privacy Policy  
The copyright of this of current website are held by JIBM. Our principal place of business is Riphah Centre of Islamic Business, Riphah International University, Al-Mizan Campus, 274- Peshawar Road Rawalpindi.  
Our approach  
Your privacy is our top priority. We ensure that once we have your information, we protect it from infringement and prevent your privacy from being violated. Our policy sheds light on this approach.  
By using this site for registration or order placement, you allow to collect, use, and convey your information according to term and condition of policy.  
Collection of information  
The sorts of individual data that the Service gathers directly from you may include:  
• Your name, Affiliation, Contact details (such as “email address, postal address and telephone number”).  
• Information regarding educational and professional background.  
• Usernames and passwords  
• Feedback, Comments and other content you submit; and  
• Preferences regarding Interests and communication

Use of information  
Your information helps us to grant you a smooth access to current “website” and aids in “administration, statistical analysis, and market research”. If users desire to order for any goods or services using this site, then they will be delivered using the information provided, specifically for billing and contacting you regarding your order.  
Cookies  
This website accepts cookies. Cookies are chunks info are provided to hard disk of your computer through “web browser”. They inform us of your activity and preferences while using our site. They do not provide personal information but only connect to your browser indirectly. Cookies also ease your login and website usage in the future. They also help us personalize our services according to your demands. If you want to manage the cookies, your browser has a help section that will alert you before accepting cookies. You can also learn how to filter or disable the cookies from there. However, if you disable cookies, certain features of the website might not work optimally.

Changes to our privacy policy:  
This privacy policy is subject to change. Any progressions will be posted on this page with a refreshed update date.  
Information regarding usage of cookies  
Current website utilizes “cookies” to differentiate between you and the other users of website. It enables deliver great service to our visitors and ameliorates the website constantly.  
Website employs “analytical cookies”. These enable to identify and calculate number of visitors and determine their patterns of website usage. It also helps to improve website's functioning; e.g. Through make sure the users about they are able to search and they want to search without difficulty.
